<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>132 Minutes on Beansie&#39;s Movie Corner</title>
        <link>https://beansie76.github.io/tags/132-minutes/</link>
        <description>Recent content in 132 Minutes on Beansie&#39;s Movie Corner</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://beansie76.github.io/tags/132-minutes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Die Hard</title>
        <link>https://beansie76.github.io/p/die-hard/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://beansie76.github.io/p/die-hard/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://beansie76.github.io/p/die-hard/die-hard.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Die Hard" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Die Hard&amp;rdquo; is an action movie that&amp;rsquo;s essentially an adrenaline-packed ride from start to finish. It stars Bruce Willis in the role of New York cop John McClane, who finds himself single-handedly taking on a group of terrorists in a Los Angeles skyscraper. Released in 1988, the film boasts thrilling action sequences and memorable one-liners that have since become synonymous with the genre itself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The plot of &amp;ldquo;Die Hard&amp;rdquo; is straight-forward: it&amp;rsquo;s essentially a game of cat-and-mouse between McClane and the terrorists. The movie&amp;rsquo;s pacing keeps viewers on the edge of their seats, offering no reprieve from the relentless action. Willis&amp;rsquo; performance is commendable; he effortlessly portrays the everyman-turned-hero with a believable mix of grit and vulnerability.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, &amp;ldquo;Die Hard&amp;rdquo; is a benchmark in the action genre. While it may not delve deeply into character complexities or societal critiques, it is undeniably effective in delivering high-stakes thrills. Its legacy is evident in the many action movies that have tried to replicate its successful formula since its release. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re an action aficionado or just in for some classic 80s cinema, &amp;ldquo;Die Hard&amp;rdquo; is a must-watch.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5 Bags of Popcorn&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
