<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>2003 on Beansie&#39;s Movie Corner</title>
        <link>https://beansie76.github.io/tags/2003/</link>
        <description>Recent content in 2003 on Beansie&#39;s Movie Corner</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:52:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://beansie76.github.io/tags/2003/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Anger Management</title>
        <link>https://beansie76.github.io/p/anger-management/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://beansie76.github.io/p/anger-management/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://beansie76.github.io/p/anger-management/anger-management.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Anger Management" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Anger Management,&amp;rdquo; the 2003 film that pairs Adam Sandler and Jack Nicholson, is a whirlwind of comedy. Sandler, in his well-known everyman persona, is Dave Buznik, a man who, despite being calm and composed, lands in an anger management program. Nicholson, on the other hand, is the eccentric therapist Dr. Buddy Rydell, whose unconventional techniques form the crux of the film&amp;rsquo;s humor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The interplay between Sandler and Nicholson delivers an abundance of laughs. The scenarios Dave finds himself in, thanks to Dr. Buddy&amp;rsquo;s odd techniques, are as absurd as they are hilarious. The film flits from one comedic setup to another, and this rhythm keeps the fun alive. All the while, the film&amp;rsquo;s theme, anger management, is handled with a light touch, keeping the film from becoming overly serious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Anger Management&amp;rdquo; certainly ticks the boxes for an enjoyable comedy. It rides high on the performances of its leading actors and its absurd situations. If you&amp;rsquo;re after a movie that keeps things light and fun while offering a steady supply of laughs, then this is a film that fits the bill. It&amp;rsquo;s a comedic romp with Sandler and Nicholson steering the ship, offering an entertaining escape for the duration of the movie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5 Bags of Popcorn&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
