<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Comedy on Beansie&#39;s Movie Corner</title>
        <link>https://beansie76.github.io/tags/comedy/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Comedy on Beansie&#39;s Movie Corner</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:53:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://beansie76.github.io/tags/comedy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Muppet Treasure Island</title>
        <link>https://beansie76.github.io/p/muppet-treasure-island/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://beansie76.github.io/p/muppet-treasure-island/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://beansie76.github.io/p/muppet-treasure-island/muppet-treasure-island.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Muppet Treasure Island" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Muppets Treasure Island,&amp;rdquo; released in 1996, is a delightful take on Robert Louis Stevenson&amp;rsquo;s classic adventure tale, &amp;ldquo;Treasure Island.&amp;rdquo; The film sees our favorite Muppet characters thrust into the world of pirates and buried treasure, offering a mix of hilarity and high-seas adventure. This Brian Henson directed film continues the Muppet tradition of adapting classic tales with their unique brand of humor and charm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The film cleverly casts the Muppets in key roles, with Kermit the Frog taking on the part of Captain Smollett and Miss Piggy as the flamboyant Benjamin Gunn. Alongside the Muppets, a host of human actors add to the fun, most notably Tim Curry, who chews the scenery with great aplomb as the notorious Long John Silver. Kevin Bishop, as Jim Hawkins, also provides a solid human anchor to the Muppet antics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Muppets Treasure Island&amp;rdquo; stays faithful to the adventurous spirit of Stevenson&amp;rsquo;s original story while infusing it with Muppet-style comedy. The plot twists and turns as per the original narrative, but the film also provides plenty of opportunities for slapstick humor, breaking the fourth wall, and catchy musical numbers that Muppet fans have come to love and expect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The film also excels in its technical aspects. The puppeteering work is top-notch, bringing life and energy to the beloved Muppet characters. The sets are wonderfully crafted, evoking a sense of adventure and excitement fitting for a pirate movie. The musical numbers, composed by Barry Mann and Cynthia Weil, are memorable and fun, enhancing the film&amp;rsquo;s jovial tone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While it may not delve deep into the complexities of pirate life or provide a sober rendition of Stevenson&amp;rsquo;s classic, &amp;ldquo;Muppets Treasure Island&amp;rdquo; is undeniably entertaining. It&amp;rsquo;s a film that balances humor, adventure, and heart, showcasing the enduring appeal of the Muppets. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a Muppet enthusiast or simply a fan of lighthearted adventure films, this movie offers an enjoyable and laughter-filled viewing experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5 Bags of Popcorn&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Anger Management</title>
        <link>https://beansie76.github.io/p/anger-management/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://beansie76.github.io/p/anger-management/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://beansie76.github.io/p/anger-management/anger-management.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Anger Management" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Anger Management,&amp;rdquo; the 2003 film that pairs Adam Sandler and Jack Nicholson, is a whirlwind of comedy. Sandler, in his well-known everyman persona, is Dave Buznik, a man who, despite being calm and composed, lands in an anger management program. Nicholson, on the other hand, is the eccentric therapist Dr. Buddy Rydell, whose unconventional techniques form the crux of the film&amp;rsquo;s humor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The interplay between Sandler and Nicholson delivers an abundance of laughs. The scenarios Dave finds himself in, thanks to Dr. Buddy&amp;rsquo;s odd techniques, are as absurd as they are hilarious. The film flits from one comedic setup to another, and this rhythm keeps the fun alive. All the while, the film&amp;rsquo;s theme, anger management, is handled with a light touch, keeping the film from becoming overly serious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Anger Management&amp;rdquo; certainly ticks the boxes for an enjoyable comedy. It rides high on the performances of its leading actors and its absurd situations. If you&amp;rsquo;re after a movie that keeps things light and fun while offering a steady supply of laughs, then this is a film that fits the bill. It&amp;rsquo;s a comedic romp with Sandler and Nicholson steering the ship, offering an entertaining escape for the duration of the movie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5 Bags of Popcorn&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Madea Goes to Jail</title>
        <link>https://beansie76.github.io/p/madea-goes-to-jail/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 06:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://beansie76.github.io/p/madea-goes-to-jail/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://beansie76.github.io/p/madea-goes-to-jail/madea-goes-to-jail.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Madea Goes to Jail" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Madea Goes to Jail,&amp;rdquo; released in 2009, is another addition to Tyler Perry&amp;rsquo;s popular Madea franchise. The film once again centers on the larger-than-life character, Mabel &amp;ldquo;Madea&amp;rdquo; Simmons, whose no-nonsense attitude and eccentric behavior often land her in hilariously unusual situations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this installment, Madea&amp;rsquo;s reckless behavior catches up with her as she ends up behind bars. While this plot could potentially offer an in-depth look at the American penal system through a comedic lens, the film primarily focuses on delivering laughs through Madea&amp;rsquo;s unconventional prison antics. Tyler Perry, who not only writes and directs but also stars as the formidable Madea, brings his signature brand of humor to the screen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, &amp;ldquo;Madea Goes to Jail&amp;rdquo; is a comedy that delivers in terms of amusement and eccentricity, much like its predecessors. Although it doesn&amp;rsquo;t offer a deep examination of its characters or a profound commentary on society, it excels in providing comedic relief. If you&amp;rsquo;re a fan of the franchise or just looking for a light-hearted, funny movie to unwind with, &amp;ldquo;Madea Goes to Jail&amp;rdquo; is a good pick.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5 Bags of Popcorn&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
