<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>99 Minutes on Beansie&#39;s Movie Corner</title>
        <link>https://beansie76.github.io/tags/99-minutes/</link>
        <description>Recent content in 99 Minutes on Beansie&#39;s Movie Corner</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:53:54 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://beansie76.github.io/tags/99-minutes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Muppet Treasure Island</title>
        <link>https://beansie76.github.io/p/muppet-treasure-island/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 11:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://beansie76.github.io/p/muppet-treasure-island/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://beansie76.github.io/p/muppet-treasure-island/muppet-treasure-island.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Muppet Treasure Island" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Muppets Treasure Island,&amp;rdquo; released in 1996, is a delightful take on Robert Louis Stevenson&amp;rsquo;s classic adventure tale, &amp;ldquo;Treasure Island.&amp;rdquo; The film sees our favorite Muppet characters thrust into the world of pirates and buried treasure, offering a mix of hilarity and high-seas adventure. This Brian Henson directed film continues the Muppet tradition of adapting classic tales with their unique brand of humor and charm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The film cleverly casts the Muppets in key roles, with Kermit the Frog taking on the part of Captain Smollett and Miss Piggy as the flamboyant Benjamin Gunn. Alongside the Muppets, a host of human actors add to the fun, most notably Tim Curry, who chews the scenery with great aplomb as the notorious Long John Silver. Kevin Bishop, as Jim Hawkins, also provides a solid human anchor to the Muppet antics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Muppets Treasure Island&amp;rdquo; stays faithful to the adventurous spirit of Stevenson&amp;rsquo;s original story while infusing it with Muppet-style comedy. The plot twists and turns as per the original narrative, but the film also provides plenty of opportunities for slapstick humor, breaking the fourth wall, and catchy musical numbers that Muppet fans have come to love and expect.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The film also excels in its technical aspects. The puppeteering work is top-notch, bringing life and energy to the beloved Muppet characters. The sets are wonderfully crafted, evoking a sense of adventure and excitement fitting for a pirate movie. The musical numbers, composed by Barry Mann and Cynthia Weil, are memorable and fun, enhancing the film&amp;rsquo;s jovial tone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While it may not delve deep into the complexities of pirate life or provide a sober rendition of Stevenson&amp;rsquo;s classic, &amp;ldquo;Muppets Treasure Island&amp;rdquo; is undeniably entertaining. It&amp;rsquo;s a film that balances humor, adventure, and heart, showcasing the enduring appeal of the Muppets. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a Muppet enthusiast or simply a fan of lighthearted adventure films, this movie offers an enjoyable and laughter-filled viewing experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5 Bags of Popcorn&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
