<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>PG-13 Rating on Beansie&#39;s Movie Corner</title>
        <link>https://beansie76.github.io/tags/pg-13-rating/</link>
        <description>Recent content in PG-13 Rating on Beansie&#39;s Movie Corner</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 06:00:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://beansie76.github.io/tags/pg-13-rating/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Madea Goes to Jail</title>
        <link>https://beansie76.github.io/p/madea-goes-to-jail/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 06:00:59 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://beansie76.github.io/p/madea-goes-to-jail/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://beansie76.github.io/p/madea-goes-to-jail/madea-goes-to-jail.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Madea Goes to Jail" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Madea Goes to Jail,&amp;rdquo; released in 2009, is another addition to Tyler Perry&amp;rsquo;s popular Madea franchise. The film once again centers on the larger-than-life character, Mabel &amp;ldquo;Madea&amp;rdquo; Simmons, whose no-nonsense attitude and eccentric behavior often land her in hilariously unusual situations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this installment, Madea&amp;rsquo;s reckless behavior catches up with her as she ends up behind bars. While this plot could potentially offer an in-depth look at the American penal system through a comedic lens, the film primarily focuses on delivering laughs through Madea&amp;rsquo;s unconventional prison antics. Tyler Perry, who not only writes and directs but also stars as the formidable Madea, brings his signature brand of humor to the screen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, &amp;ldquo;Madea Goes to Jail&amp;rdquo; is a comedy that delivers in terms of amusement and eccentricity, much like its predecessors. Although it doesn&amp;rsquo;t offer a deep examination of its characters or a profound commentary on society, it excels in providing comedic relief. If you&amp;rsquo;re a fan of the franchise or just looking for a light-hearted, funny movie to unwind with, &amp;ldquo;Madea Goes to Jail&amp;rdquo; is a good pick.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5 Bags of Popcorn&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
